Support for NPR Music comes from Capital
1, proud supporters of NPR Music and the
Tiny Desk Contest. What's in your
wallet? Learn more at capital1.com.
Hold me baby.
Hold me close.
Cheek to cheek and nose to nose.
Kiss me darling.
Kiss me right. Uhhuh. If you do
[singing] it good, we'll be kissing all
night.
Cuz I've been looking for your kind of
love all my life.
I can be a good woman to you day and
night.
Are you ready to love me, baby? I'm
ready to love you, baby. Are you ready
to love me, baby?
Well, hello, Tiny D.
I've been looking for your kind of love
all my life.
I can be a good woman to you. Do you
know?
Are you ready to love me, baby? I'm
ready to love you, baby. Are you ready
to love me, baby?
Are you ready to love me, baby? I'm
ready to love you, baby. Are you
[singing] ready to love me, baby?
>> All right, everybody. Come on. Like
this. Yeah.
Are you ready?
>> Are you ready?
>> Are you
ready?
>> Are you ready to love me?
>> Are you ready to love me, baby?
>> Love you.
>> Are you ready to love you?
[music]
>> Love me.
>> I love you.
>> I'm ready to love you. [music] Love me.
Love me. Love you. Love you. Love me.
Yeah, it [music]
feel
everybody.
Here we go.
Woo!
Leaving [singing]
so soon
like we just arrived.
Did I play [singing] the right tune
for your pleasure tonight?
Stay [singing]
with me. [music]
Don't leave just yet. We count.
So please forget about
tomorrow. [screaming]
Five more minutes. Five more minutes.
[music and singing]
I need five more minutes to love.
[music]
Five [singing] more minutes. Five more
minutes. [music]
I need five more minutes to [singing]
love.
Come on, clap your hands like this
everybody. Next time now
don't leave yet. We got all night. So
please [singing]
[screaming]
[music]
here we go.
Wow.
[music]
>> DC TINY DANCE. [cheering]
>> YEAH.
>> My name is Michael Troder Jr.
>> and I'm Tanya [music] Troder. We are the
War and Treaty and we are husband and
wife and we're happy to be here. We love
you. This song is called Don't Say
Goodbye.
Even though we're going to say goodbye
to y'all. We don't want to, but we love
you. Here it go.
[music]
I don't want [music]
another
one night [singing] stand.
I know [singing] what you want
is a man with a slow hand.
[singing and music]
Oh yeah. Yeah.
And I don't need
a temporary
connection.
[singing]
What I need
is a permanent
situation.
Don't say goodbye.
Don't say farewell.
Don't say so long without a kiss.
telling me you're coming back. Don't say
goodbye.
Don't say good night.
Don't [music and singing] say so long
without a kiss telling me you're coming
back.
Please [singing and music]
come back to me.
Darling.
>> All right, DC. [singing] Just snap your
fingers like this. I want to [music] be
alone tonight.
>> This is the spirit of ask for assistance
in the building today.
>> I don't want nothing.
>> I don't want to be alone tonight.
>> Don't want to be Don't want to be Don't
want nothing.
[music] Don't say goodbye, baby. Don't
say goodbye, baby. [music]
Don't say goodbye, baby. [singing]
Don't say goodbye.
Don't say [music] goodbye.
Please [singing] come back to me.
Oh,
please [music] come back to me,
darling. [singing]
>> [music]
[cheering]
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you so [applause] much.
>> Thank you. We in the spirit of humanity,
in the spirit of love, we're introduce
you all to our musical family. Over here
on vocals is Christina and Jordan.
[applause]
>> And back here on keys is Corey Keys.
And on guitar, our longest running
member, Max Brown.
[applause]
And back here on drums, we just call him
Bam. Miss Bam.
>> Bam.
And on horns, we got my man COLTON AND
BLAZE.
>> [applause]
>> AND LAST but not least, the troublemaker
of the bunch, our music director, Mr.
Darien Hajj. Give it up for Darien.
[applause]
>> We want to quickly get into this song.
This song is called Shouldn't Have. It's
not about me.
>> Just know that.
>> It's not, but you know.
Shouldn't
have been gone [screaming]
that long, baby.
I should have stay
stayed out that way.
I'm
shouldn't have gone
that long. Baby,
I should have took
that dinner game.
Oh,
YOU EXPECTED MORE FROM ME.
You let me be in her company.
How could I be [singing]
so wrong?
I crossed the line. [singing]
I did it this time. How could I lose
control? [music]
I was wrong. Knew all along.
How could I hurt
you? [screaming] I MESSED up so bad
making [singing] you mad. But baby, I
want you to [singing]
said if it ever
[music]
happens again,
>> mama, you got to let me let me
[screaming]
>> [music]
>> You just got to let me go. Baby
[singing]
talk to a mama.
You shouldn't have been down.
Hello, baby.
I thought you were
better.
[singing]
You should have been gone
that long. Baby
hurting me this way.
Oh, now it wasn't.
[music]
You should have had more respect for me
in your heart. You see,
how can I forive you?
>> [screaming]
>> You cross the line. You did it this
time.
Baby lo.
[singing]
You are wrong. [music]
>> I knew it all along.
How could you hurt? How could you? Oh,
you messed up so bad. I'm so damn mad.
Baby, want [music] you to [singing] know
that if it ever happens again,
>> I got to I got to let you go.
I got to let you go.
How could you, baby? [singing]
>> How could you hurt me?
>> Maybe I messed up real bad when I heard
you. [singing]
You're breaking my heart. [screaming]
>> You're breaking my heart.
Look what we build together.
I don't know. Don't let me go, baby.
[music]
[screaming]
[screaming] O
said I messed up the [singing] bad.
[music]
[applause]
[cheering]
>> Well,
>> thank you.
>> We got one more song. [applause]
Um, this song we wrote, I was just
thinking about everyone who walks in
high heels every day going through some
high heel kind of stuff.
>> That's right.
>> Yeah.
>> I uh had some cowboy boots on.
>> You
>> And I finally got the slight taste of
what it feels like to walk in heels.
[laughter]
>> And I had on two inch. They call them my
the band. They told me I had on auntie
heels. So, I wouldn't put on some real
high heels. They were clowning me back
here. [laughter]
>> But again, uh we salute y'all and we
dedicate this song to y'all. This song
is called High Heels. And we have a
very, very special guest. It's our home
girl, ladies and gentlemen, Dr. Chelsea
Green.
[cheering and applause]
[applause]
>> Chelse, ready?
All right. High heels.
[music]
You clap like this.
Hey, [music] these boots are made for
styling
profiling around my hood.
Them girls be strutting this stuff.
Them boys [music and singing] be up to
no good
past.
gets across my eyes.
Them girls be you. You looking mama. But
she gives you a pass.
She's so [music]
she's
she's working. Come on. She go and she
goes.
>> She goes
Oh.
Oh,
[music] singing over in high heels in
high heels.
High heels.
She [music]
high.
Take
>> it to the bridge. Let's go.
Baby, she working it.
Mama's doing her thing.
Come on. [music]
Come on.
Come on. [screaming]
She's the
She's a girl. [music]
I was working and she's a work. [music]
Jesus.
I
he
[music]
Thank
Let's go.
[music]
Thank you.
>> Thank you.
[applause and cheering]
>> Thank y'all [cheering] so much.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> Thank you. [applause]
Thank you.
[cheering]
>> Thank y'all so much for coming.
Thanks for watching. Support for NPR
Music comes from Riven, makers of all
electric adventure vehicles, including
the R1S three row SUV. More at riv.com.
A quick update before you go. We're
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
[music] by September 12th, 2026, and you
and a friend could win a free trip to DC
to see a Tiny Desk concert live in
person. You even get to choose which
upcoming show you want to see. And it's
completely free to enter. Just go to
npr.org/tinyes
giveaway. Entering is completely free,
but you can get more entries by snagging
some limited edition Tiny Desk merch or
by making a special donation to the NPR
network. Learn more and enter today at
npr.org/tinyes
giveaway.